sharepowered.com 2018-01-24

# Privacy policy

This privacy statement shows our commitment to the privacy of our customers and users of this website. This Privacy policy explains how we collects, use, maintain and discloseinformation relating to our customers and users of this website. By using this website, which displays this Privacy Policy or a link thereto, or by otherwise interacting with InFactDomains, you agree and accept the conditions stated in this Privacy Policy. In the case we made changes to our Privacy Policy, we will include these changes on this page, send an email withnotification about the changes, and statethe date when the Privacy Policy was modified. This Privacy Policy was last modified on 2/15/2016.

### Information collecting

In order to register online or purchase our goods and services, you must be at least eighteen (18) years old. We do not knowingly collect information from persons under the age of eighteen (18).

**_Contact information:_ **we collect personal information from online users through online forms, emails or other ways of correspondence. The data that we collect is information that identifies you personally, which includes: name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone numbers.

**_Financial information:_ **we do not collect financial information. All transactions are conducted through our partners 2checkout, PayPal, Escrow, all of which are well-known worldwide and provide assurances that transactionsare secure.

**_Cookies:_ **cookies are small text-files, which are sent to a user's computer by a website when the user visits the website. The file identifies the user’s computer and can store the user's preferences and other data. By using cookies, we do not collectpersonal information. We use "cookie" technology for enhancing online experience by making it easier for you to navigate through the pages and making some features work better. You can enable or disable cookies in your web browser, but please note that certain pages may not function correctly without cookies.

**_Other information:_ **we collect and store somespecific types of information whenever you interact with us. This information includesweb browser type you are using, referringpage from which you come to current page, IP address (a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet). We collect these in order to improve security, administer the website and analyze trends. We track your movement within the website and use this information to improve our website, to get statistical information and to improve the products and services we provide.

### Information use

The information we collect is used:

  * to deliver products and services to customers,
  * to enhance customer service,
  * to make our website a better experience for our customers and visitors,
  * to send periodic newsletter or e-mails with information about products, services and special offers (instructions on how to unsubscribe are at the bottom of each e-mail).

### Information maintenance and protection

Provided information is stored in one or more databases directly or indirectly maintained by InFactDomains. We employ industry-standard security measures to protect the confidentiality of the information we collect. We will make every effort to avoid data loss, misuse or alteration of data, but we cannot guarantee that thesewill not occur. As we do not collect userfinancial information (such as credit card details), user financial data cannot be misused through this website. Information disclosure InFactDomainswill not sell or otherwise share information with third parties, unless you specifically authorize such sharing of infromation. We will make every effort to preserve your privacy, but in cases when it is required by lawto comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or another legal process, or/andwe believe that it is necessary in order to protect our rights, we may need to disclose your personal information.

### Limitation of liability

InFactDomains assumes no responsibility or liability with regard to any theft, loss, alteration or misuse of personal or other information lawfully provided by InFactDomains to third parties, or with regard to failure of any third party to abide by this privacy policy or such third party's privacy policy or any agreement between that third party and InFactDomains. Contacting us If you have any questions regarding this Privacy policy, you can contact us through the contact form on our [Contact us](http://sharepowered.com/contact-us) page on this web site,or you can email us: [support@infactdomains.com](mailto:support@infactdomains.com).
